The end will be WCKD.
Maze Runner: The Death Cure is a science fiction,
action, adventure film directed by Wes Ball.
Thomas leads his group of escaped Gladers on their
final and most dangerous mission yet.
To save their friends, they must break into the legendary Last City, a
WCKD-controlled labyrinth that may turn out to be the deadliest maze of all.
Anyone who makes it out alive will get answers to the questions the
Gladers have been asking since they first arrived in the maze.
Thomas, played by Dylan O'Brien.
Teresa Agnes, played by Kaya Scodelario.
Newt, played by Thomas Brodie-Sangster.
Minho, played by Ki Hong Lee.
Frypan, played by Dexter Darden.
Brenda, played by Rosa Salazar.
Maze Runner: The Death Cure (also known simply as The Death Cure) is a 2018 American
dystopian science fiction film directed by Wes Ball and with a screenplay by T.
Nowlin, based on the 2011 novel The Death Cure written by James Dashner.
It is the sequel to the 2015 film Maze Runner: The Scorch Trials and the
third and final installment in the Maze Runner film series.
Dylan O'Brien, Kaya Scodelario, Thomas Brodie-Sangster, Patricia Clarkson, Ki Hong Lee, Dexter Darden, Giancarlo Esposito, Aidan Gillen, Barry Pepper, Nathalie
Emmanuel, Jacob Lofland, Katherine McNamara, Rosa Salazar, and Will Poulter reprise their roles from the previous films with Walton Goggins joining the cast.
Maze Runner: The Death Cure was originally set to be released on February 17, 2017, in the United States by 20th Century Fox, but the studio
rescheduled the film's release for January 26, 2018, allowing time for O'Brien to recover from injuries he sustained during filming.
The film received mixed reviews from critics with praise for the cast performances, action sequences and
visual effects but criticism for the storyline, screenplay and character development.
The film grossed over $288 million worldwide.
The film explores themes of based on novel or book, fight,
maze, post-apocalyptic future, imprisonment.
The tone is thought_provoking and intense.